Jaturong Duangchaiyusuk, Team Lead & Senior Developer

Email: jaturong.duang@gmail.com Mobile: (+66) 86 906 8319

Date of Birth: 6 Feb 1990 Nationality: Thai Gender: Male

Github: https://github.com/srankmeng
Website: https://srankmeng.github.io/personal-web

Summary / Profile:

I have experience with 10+ years of Web development. For technical skills such as frontend, backend, automated testing, and AWS services (EC2, S3, Lambda, Cloudfront, etc.). I'm good on the frontend more than the backend but I can do it as well. For other skills, I used to use the Agile process in my projects which have planning, backlog refinement, daily stand up, and retrospective. And I can use tools that are related to my tasks. In addition, I supported the team like a review code, coaching team members, and finding solutions when having problems delivering tasks on time for team success.

Employment History:

May 2021 - Jul 2022

Team Lead Developer, Redlamp Co., Ltd.

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & clearing issue blocks for delivering the project on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Nest js for web development
- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Use Cypress for E2E automate part
- The delivery website which client site and back-office site

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Senior Backend Developer, SCB

Bangkok, Thailand

- Join in Robinhood application team
- Develop API in OTA feature (online travel agency), connect 3rd party api
- Maintain existing feature
- Use AWS service to support the feature
- Develop the unit test to support the feature
- Meeting and discussing with the team

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021

Team Lead Developer, SCG

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery of projects on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Flask for web development

- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Delivery website https://www.scg-id.com that includes back-office site

Jan 2017 - Dec 2019

Frontend Team Lead & Senior Developer, Lqid 360 Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery of projects on time
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use React, Redux for frontend web development
- Motivation team members and making teamwork
- Use jest for unit test
- Discussing with backend team for design response api
- Delivery KYC's back-office
- Delivery chat system use in back-office with WebRTC technology
- Delivery monitoring system display with chart

May 2012 - Dec 2016

Frontend Developer

Bangkok, Thailand

- Created HTML & CSS related to designs
- Use jquery to manage data on the frontend side
- Use Angularjs v1 to manage data on the frontend side
- Integrate API and display data
- Delivery BigC check QC back-office
- Delivery E-commerce web
- Support team & issues

Educations:

May 2008 - Apr 2012

Computer Engineering Bachelor's Degree Bangkok, Thailand
King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang (KMITL)

Skills:

Javascript Jest Skillful Expert Vue, Nuxt Docker Expert Experienced **AWS** React, Redux Skillful Experienced **React Native** Skillful Github Action Skillful Html & CSS Agile Expert Experienced Jquery Odoo Skillful Expert Bootstrap MongoDB Skillful Expert Nest js, Node js PostgresSQL & MySQL Skillful Experienced **Typescript** Cypress Skillful Experienced

	Python	Skillful	Git	Expert
	Liff	Skillful	Firebase	Skillful
Languages:	Thai	Native	English	good command

Hobbies:

Cinema, Japanese manga, Watching football, Beer